[{"answer": "I loved her my friend, I loved her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "And she loved me. my friend, ho, she really did", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "No, you didn't", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No she didn't", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Whyie", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'm not going to see that nut doctor she went to that place with", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "... date with my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "He's not THAT religious", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Now what does the little man inside you say? See you gotta listen to the little man", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "The little man knows all", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "My little man doesn't know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "My little man's an idiot", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " What smell", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hello. my friend, come in. Come in I've heard an awful lot about you. Please sit down", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "So uh, she broke up with you? ..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well come here and take a look", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "So, what's that", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What? So what? It's a nipple. A little round circular protuberance. What's the big deal? See everybody's got them. See I got them", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Everybody's got them.", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You're gonna rip it. You're gonna rip it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Okay. Uh, my mother is is going to pay for the sessions. ... Oh,my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well every day for the past four days she hasn't returned one call", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "It was a scratch", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "But that's not what she thinks", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "All right. I'll call the agency.  Hello. Yes, I'm trying to get in touch with my friend. Do you know if she's been in town? She's been in town. Oh really. well thank you very much.  She has been in town. She's at my friend's right now", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "People don't change", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'm not a soft boiled egg", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Oh, yes kramer. I uh, think I know something about this. Will you excuse us my friend?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Neither do I.", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What are you doing here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Well, I've been busy", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pick.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Oh, you've never missed a button?!  Yeah?.", "qsentId": 34}]